QOTRUNNADA OKTIRIANI

Undergraduate Informatics Student

Banyumas, Indonesia | Phone: 082241443663 | Email: qotrunnadaoktiriani@gmail.com | LinkedIn: qotrunnadao | Github: qotrunnadao

SUMMARY

Undergraduate informatics student at Jenderal Soedirman University. I have experience in developing web applications using Laravel Framework, familiar with designing and managing instagram feeds and I'm also interested in Frontend Web Developer. Enjoy exploring about website design, likes to learn new things and seek many experience

EXPERIENCE

Outstanding Youth Indonesia (OYI) - Malang, Indonesia

Web Developer Intern (September 2021 – February 2022)

- Developing the OYI website, especially to create a newsletter feature using the Laravel framework.
- Work closely with the web developer and design division to improve the UI/UX of the OYI website.
- Post articles and events to the OYI website according to the specified schedule.
- Enter weekly progress into the trello application and have a meeting with the web developer division to explain the progress made.

CV JENDERAL SOFTWARE - Banyumas, Indonesia

Web Application Developer Intern (January 2021 - April 2021)

- create a face recognition attendance system using the laravel framework by accessing the API of a pre-existing face recognition system.
- Learn basic programming using laravel framework for 1 week followed by developing applications for 1 month at the office.
- analyze the system requirment by conducting interviews with the CEO at CV jenderal software, making mockup, UML designs and testing using blackbox testing.

EDUCATION

JENDERAL SOEDIRMAN UNIVERSITY (2018 - Present)

8th semester at Informatics Major, Faculty of Engineering - GPA 3.76

PORTFOLIO

Final Study Management System at engineering faculty of Jenderal Soedirman
University

web application built using laravel framework. used to manage the final study process at the engineering faculty of Jenderal Soedriman University.

• Employee Attendance System Using Faceprint at CV Jenderal Software combines face recognition technology into the attendance system using an API, built with the larayel framework

• Personal Website Portfolio

built using HTML, CSS and JavaScript, and already has a responsive display

SKILLS

Hard Skills:

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- Laravel
- PHP
- Git
- API
- Bootstrap

Soft Skills:

- Communication
- Teamwork
- Problem solving
- Responsible
- Positivity